kaakateeya.com 2001-06-03

# Kaakateeya.com - Largest Collection of Indian Matrimonials

This confirms that kaakateeya.com is a licensee of the TRUSTe Privacy Program. TRUSTe is an independent, non-profit organization whose mission is to build users' trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use of fair information practices. Because this web site wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices reviewed for compliance by TRUSTe. By displaying the TRUSTe trustmark, this web site has agreed to notify you of: 

1\. What personally identifiable information of yours or third party personally identifiable information that is collected  from you through the web site   
2\. The organization collecting the information   
3\. How the information is used   
4\. With whom the information may be shared   
5\. What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information   
6\. The kind of security procedures that are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under kaakateeya.com control   
7\. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information. 

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact (Krishna Yalamanchi,Customer Support) by email at krishna@kaakateeya.com.   
If you do not receive acknowledgment of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should then contact [TRUSTe](http://www.truste.org/watchdog.html). TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with the Web site to resolve your concerns. 

By using our site, you consent to the collection and use of your information as described in this Privacy Policy. Any changes to our Privacy Policy will be reflected on this page so that you are always aware of the information we collect and how we use it. 

**Registration**   
In order to use this website, a user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give their contact information (such as name and email address). This information is used to contact the user about the services on our site for which they have expressed interest. It is optional for the user to provide demographic information (such as income level and gender), and unique identifiers (such as social security number), but encouraged so we can provide a more personalized experience on our site.   
Kaakateeya.com and its partners/ offices in India collect personal information necessary to respond to your requests for customized matrimonial services and to allow you to use the resources available on our website. Personal information includes, but is not limited to, name, physical address, email address, date of birth, religion, time of birth, caste, fathers name, mothers name, brothers and sisters details phone number, age and any other information that itself identifies or, when tied to the above information, may identify you as a specific individual. Kaakateeya.com and its partners. Kaakateeya.com also uses order forms, feedback for you to request certain information, products and services. On such order forms, we collect your contact information, financial information (We work with Card Service International and we do not store your credit card details on our site like the credit card no, address and other related information) and demographic information. 

**Advanced Registration**   
Kaakateeya.com offers paid membership to user wishing to use our advance features such as Contact Information of other Registered Members, Membership to our Indian Offices. Here a user must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customer's orders. If we have trouble processing an order, this contact information is used to get in touch with the user. 

**Cookies**   
kaakateeya.com does not use any cookies. 

**Log Files**   
We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

**Sharing**   
We do not share your personal information with anybody. We will share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. We use an outside shipping company to ship orders, and a credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes. We partner with another party to provide specific services. When the user signs up for these services, we will share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services. 

**Links**   
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we kaakateeya.com are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. 

**Newsletter**   
If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter, we ask for contact information such as name and email address. 

**Surveys & Contests**   
From time-to-time our site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site. 

**Tell-A-Friend**   
If a user elects to use our referral service for informing a friend about our site, we ask them for the friend’s name and email address. kaakateeya.com will automatically send the friend a one-time email inviting them to visit the site. kaakateeya.com stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email. The friend may contact kaakateeya.com at http://www.kaakateeya.com/cfm/mailing_list.cfm to request the removal of this information from their database. 

**Security**

Kaakateeya.com is a verisign secure site. Click the Image to verify. 

This website takes every precaution to protect our users’ information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line.   
When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when you are just ‘surfing’. To learn more about SSL, follow this link [Verisign](http://www.verisign.com/)   
While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our users’ information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Our employees must use password-protected screen-savers when they leave their desk. When they return, they must re-enter their password to re-gain access to your information. Furthermore, ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Every quarter, as well as any time new policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our customers’ information is protected. Finally, the servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure environment, behind a locked cage.   
If you have any questions about the security at our website, you can send an email to info@kaakateeya.com. 

**Supplementation of Information**   
Email Messages, Registration Forms, and other related forms. We make the contents of the registration form visible to you and other register members of kaakateeya.com or its offices in India. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information. You should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. In order for this website to properly fulfill its obligation to our customers, it is necessary for us to supplement the information we receive with information from 3rd party sources.   
For example, to determine if our customers qualify for one of our credit cards, we use their name and social security number to request a credit report. Once we determine a user’s credit-worthiness, this document is destroyed.   
(or)   
In order for this website to enhance its ability to tailor the site to an individual’s preference, we combine information about the purchasing habits of users with similar information from our partners, Company Y & Company Z, to create a personalized user profile. When a user makes a purchase from either of these two companies, the companies collect and share that purchase information with us so we can tailor the site to our users’ preferences. 

**Special Offers**   
We send all new members a welcoming email to verify password and username. Established members will occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, and a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications. Please see our choice and opt-out below. 

**Site and Service Updates**   
We also send the user site and service announcement updates. Members are not able to un-subscribe from service announcements, which contain important information about the service. We communicate with the user to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account via email or phone. 

**Correction/Updating Personal Information:** If a user’s personally identifiable information changes (such as your zip code), or if a user no longer desires our service, we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update or remove that user’s personal data provided to us. This can usually be done at the member information page or by emailing our Customer Support at info@kaakateeya.com. You can also use the [Modify](http://www.kaakateeya.com/cfm/modify_login.cfm) and [Delete](http://www.kaakateeya.com/cfm/delete_login.cfm) pages to modify or delete your information by logging in with your userid and password.   
However, even if you delete your personal information in our database, it maybe stored by our offices in India / USA for archival purposes. 

**Choice/Opt-out**   
Our users are given the opportunity to ‘opt-out’ of having their information used for purposes not directly related to our site at the point where we ask for the information. For example, our order form has an ‘opt-out’ mechanism so users who buy a product from us, but don’t want any marketing material, can keep their email address off of our lists.   
Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter or promotional materials from our partners may opt-out of receiving these communications by replying to unsubscribe in the subject line in the email or email us at info@kaakateeya.com You can also call us at (718) 781 6173 to be removed from the mailing list. Users of our site are always notified when their information is being collected by any outside parties. We do this so our users can make an informed choice as to whether they should proceed with services that require an outside party, or not. 

**Email Links**   
We use email links located on the "Contact us" page to allow you to contact us directly with any questions or comments you may have.   
We read every message sent in and try to reply promptly to every one. This information is used to respond directly to your questions or comments. We may also file your comments to improve the site and program, or review and discard the information. Your personal information is only shared with third parties with your explicit permission. 

**Legal Disclaimer**

**Acceptance of Terms**   
kaakateeya.com provides its service to users, subject to the following Terms of Service ("TOS"), which may be modified by us from time to time without notice to you. 

**Dsecription of Service**   
kaakateeya.com provides users with access to a variety of channels and links to other web sites. Unless explicitly stated otherwise, any new features that augment or enhance the current service shall be subject to the TOS. Membership Fee is non-refundable and non-transferable. The users understand and agree that the Service is provided "AS-IS" and that kaakateeya.com accepts no responsibility for the timeliness, deletion, non-delivery or failure to store any user communications or Contents. 

**Your Registration Obligations**   
In consideration of your use of the Service, you agree to: provide true, accurate, current and complete information about yourself as prompted by the Service's registration form (such information being the "Registration Form") and maintain and promptly update the Registration Data to keep it true, accurate, current and complete. If you provide any information that is untrue, inaccurate, not current or incomplete, or kaakateeya.com has reasonable grounds to believe that such information is untrue, inaccurate, not current or incomplete, kaakateeya.com has the right to suspend or terminate your account and refuse any and all, current or future, use of the Service (or any portion thereof). 

**Member Account,Password and Security**   
You will receive a password and account designation upon completing the Service's registration process. You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of the password and account, and are fully responsible for all activities that occur under your password or account. You agree to immediately notify kaakateeya.com of any unauthorized use of your password or account or any other breach of security, and ensure that you exit from your account at the end of each session.kaakateeya.com cannot and will not be liable for any loss or damage arising from your failure to comply with this Section. 

**Member Conduct**   
You accept that all information, data, text, software, music, sound, photographs, graphics, video, messages or other materials ("Content"), whether publicly posted or privately transmitted, are the sole responsibility of the person from which such Content originated. This means that the user, and not kaakateeya.com, is entirely responsible for all Content uploaded, posted, sent by email or otherwise transmit via the Service. kaakateeya.com does not control the Content posted via the Service and, as such, does not guarantee the accuracy, integrity or quality of such Content. You understand that by using the Service, you may be exposed to Content that is offensive, indecent or objectionable. Under no circumstances will kaakateeya.com be liable in any way for any Content, including, but not limited to, any errors or omissions in any Content, or for any loss or damage of any kind incurred as a result of the use of any Content posted, emailed or otherwise transmitted via the Service. We reserve the right to limit registration to those who will accept emails and to those who will provide the requested information. 

**Third Party Advertisers and Cookies**   
kaakateeya.com may work with a third party to serve ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. This policy only covers the use of cookies by kaakateeya.com and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. kaakateeya.com.com does not have control, nor access to the information contained in its advertisers' cookies. To find out more about how (insert name of ad server) manages the privacy of information in conjunction with serving ads on this site go to www.(name of ad server’s site).com. 

**Notification of Changes**   
We will notify you directly via email if there is a material change in our privacy practices. We will also post the changes in our privacy statement 30 days prior to a change. 

Our address   
Kaakateeya Matrimonial Wing   
118 Sanali Apts., Behind   
Kamma Sangam, Ameerpet,   
Hyderabad - 500 079   
AP India   
http://www.kaakateeya.com
